Am I imagining things, or have you
been neglecting my revenge lately?!
W-Well...
It's been a month since the kidnapping.
Kate's testimony revealed several facts
about the mysterious Daeg Gallus.
Kiriki kirikuku.
The "spell" Lady Lily left behind was
one of the organization's passwords.
Their goal is to steal her key.
I decided to give it to His Lordship
and ask him to investigate it himself.
The kidnapper had a sun tattoo,
so we think he was
a member of Daeg Gallus,
but someone assassinated him in jail
before he could be questioned.
Witnesses placed
Crown Princess Cecilia in the vicinity.
Now tell me,
why are we calling on Abigail?
To meet with Viscountess Aisha Huxley.
You said you had business with her
at Baroness Godwin's ball, remember?
Oh, her.
She might ignore a request
for a meeting from a girl like me,
so I thought I'd ask
the House of O'Brian for a favor.
It's so good to see you, Constance.
It's been too long, Lady Abigail.
My, but you are pretty!
Those amethyst eyes
and that scarlet dress...
Why, you could be a princess!
Huh?
I see you have taste, girl.
W-Wait... Huh? What?!
I understand the situation.
I'll see to it that you receive
an invitation from the Huxleys soon.
You mean you believe me?
You've puzzled me
all the while I've known you.
But if Scarlett's by your side,
that explains it.
Say, Scarlett, can you hear me?
She's over there, Abby!
Thank you, Lucia.
Your execution pained me deeply,
so allow me to assist you.
Really? I wish you'd confine your jokes
to that squashed frog you call a face.
Um... She says, yes, she understands!
I don't doubt
she's insulting me as we speak.
I had no idea that anyone but me
could see Scarlett.
My niece Lucia here
was born with keen intuition.
If anyone else has eyes
like hers, it would be...
Viscount Hamsworth, I suppose.
They say he has the goddesses' favor.
Does he really?
I've heard tell that the viscount
can see unearthly beings.
Do you not think so, my lady?
It couldn't be... Could it?
Forget that nouveau riche hog.
We're leaving, Connie.
I do hope you'll speak
to your fiancé about my request.
Oh, yes.
Now, if you'll excuse me!
Teresa Jennings lost her life
in an attempted murder-suicide.
Her husband, Kevin Jennings,
has become an invalid.
As far as Lady Abigail
was able to discover,
Daeg Gallus is selling the
hallucinogen "Jackal's Paradise."
Forget all that and get what happened
ten years ago out of Aisha.
Speaking of which,
what was Aisha Huxley like?
Well, she used to be a gloomy, plain girl.
You could say she was part of
my entourage. Or a fan, I suppose.
If I wore a red dress, so would Aisha.
If I wore blue, she would too.
In a similar style, no less.
She'd even do her hair like mine.
And just the once, she looked me
in the eye and spoke to me.
I want to be you.
And how did you reply?
Why, that should be obvious.
The world doesn't need
two Scarlett Castiels.
Duke Castiel.
Oh, Randolph.
What's this urgent business you mentioned?
Permit me to be blunt.
I want to know
about the Holy Grail of Eris.
Why, whatever could that be?
I'm sorry to say
the term is unfamiliar to me.
Will that be all?
Yes, for the time being.
A friendly word of warning.
Finish building your hand
before you try to play it.
That is the secret to a long life.
Let's go over what we know.
We'll start with the attempt to poison
Crown Princess Cecilia ten years ago,
when they found poison
in one of her house's water jars.
What made people
suspect you to begin with?
It went just as that schemer told you.
They found a moonbowstone
earring just like mine
lying beside the Luzes' water store.
As ill luck would have it, I'd called
at the house just hours earlier.
Was the earring really yours?
No, I had both of mine
when I first fell under suspicion.
And did you...
Tell the investigators? Of course.
Everything I wore was one-of-a-kind
from the hands of master craftsmen.
Inquiring at their workshops
would have substantiated as much.
Then why weren't you
cleared of suspicion?
I was told that, upon inspection,
one of my earrings turned out to be fake.
They claimed I'd anticipated the
investigation and prepared a replacement.
In other words,
someone swapped one of mine
for the one found at the Luze estate
while it was in the Security Force's safe.
Who would do such a thing?
I don't know. But in the end,
the king authorized a search of my home.
No one would dare touch the Castiel
residence without a royal order.
Then, as you know, a half-empty vial
of poison turned up in my chambers,
and they marched me off to a cell.
Did you suspect Crown Princess Cecilia?
I suppose. She did benefit
the most from my death.
So until just recently, I thought
she'd orchestrated the whole thing.
Only until recently?
To be frank, I'm not sure anymore.
I mean, she doesn't seem
the least bit satisfied.
After ten whole years, she seems
to loathe Enrique as much as ever.
And she doesn't seem attached
to wealth or power, either.
I wonder what she's trying to achieve.
I suppose we're still far from the truth.
True. But we have more than
the events of ten years ago to go on.
Something is happening now, and we can
be certain Cecilia has a hand in it.
Do you remember what
that red-haired reporter woman said?
Cecilia Luze was a whore's daughter
raised in an orphanage.
And Kevin Jennings, who got close
to the truth, wound up an addict.
Oh, that's right.
That merchant visiting her the very day
the seventh prince of Faris was abducted
lines up too perfectly to be happenstance.
The merchant's name was,
um... Vado, wasn't it?
Come to think of it, didn't the kidnapper
have an accomplice called Salvador?
The names bear a similarity on paper.
Coincidence, do you think?
If they are the same person,
then we can assume Cecilia is
involved with Daeg Gallus as well.
And that they have a hand in distributing
Jackal's Paradise on Rosenkreuz Street.
That young lady who collapsed at
the Earl John Doe Ball, Kiara Grafton,
used that hallucinogen, didn't she?
And so did Kevin Jennings.
Then Prince Ulysses's abduction,
Kate's kidnapping,
and the spread of Jackal's Paradise
are all Daeg Gallus's doing?
You're forgetting one important thing.
Daeg Gallus attacked you as well.
Kate Lorraine's kidnapper
was after Lily's key, wasn't he?
Yes.
I just said that something's afoot now,
but that isn't precisely correct.
Something has been afoot
for the past ten years...
right here in Adelbide.
I'd be surprised if it had
nothing to do with my execution.
True.
Whatever it is, Lady Lily probably
lost her life because of it.
"Destroy the Holy Grail of Eris"
was her final message.
We still don't know what it means.
Um, Your Lordship...
Yes?
I realize we're to share information,
but why at a museum?
It holds donations from
the Orlamunde family.
I thought they might
offer a clue to the key.
I visited here with Lily as well.
Of course...
They were on a first-name basis.
Of course.
Learn some tact!
Here lies one of the holy books Saint
Anastasia received from the goddesses.
What's wrong? Are you hungry?
Oh, no! I mean...
As for Abigail's request,
it will take some time.
The crown princess owns the hospital
where Kevin Jennings is a patient.
I'll need to go through
bothersome formalities.
I understand.
Scarlett and I went over
what happened ten years ago,
and she says her earring was switched.
I read the file on the earrings.
The one deemed an imitation
wasn't made of moonbowstone
but rather a type of shell
called silver-shell.
And what of the design?
U-Um, Scarlett would like to know
how the design compared.
It was identical to her own earrings.
Silver-shell doesn't circulate
by many routes.
I looked up who'd bought any at the time
and found a familiar name:
the Spencer family.
Isn't that...
It's Aisha's maiden name.
The Spencers own several workshops
that work with precious metals.
I wouldn't be surprised if Aisha
had replicas of my earrings made.
You said you planned to visit
the Huxleys to question her?
Y-Yes.
She may be involved with Daeg Gallus.
Don't do anything rash.
I won't.
I still don't feel a thing.
I don't remember anything either.
Was I really executed here?
Constance Grail...
I never dreamed she'd use
Abigail O'Brian to get to me.
Why do people say such a dull girl
reminds them of the Scarlett Castiel?
No one could ever take her place.
She is my goddess.
You're Aisha Spencer, aren't you?
You've been watching me.
Just now, and earlier as well.
What do you want?
How do you know, um, m-my name?
Why, you introduced yourself
once at some other party.
Y-You remember?
Naturally.
To whom do you imagine you're speaking?
Welcome, Miss Grail. I'm sorry
the house isn't much to look at.
Not at all.
I sincerely appreciate
your invitation, Lady Huxley.
We're only lesser nobility.
I was shocked to receive
a messenger from the O'Brians,
though he came bearing
a request from the Grails.
I hope you'll forgive me.
I simply had to see you.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to ask you a question.
If it's one I can answer, go ahead.
What is that smell?
An acquaintance of mine has
an excellent nose and memory.
She could tell the instant you appeared.
Tell me, Lady Huxley, why do you carry
the scent of Jackal's Paradise?
She noticed?!
Whatever are you talking about?
Jackal's Paradise? That hallucinogen
that was all the rage a decade ago?
You must be mistaken.
I am wearing a rare perfume today.
Perhaps that's what you smell.
It comes from a distant land.
I doubt you've heard of it.
You're a laughably poor liar.
H-How terribly rude!
I won't stand for this! Leave at once!
Dear me.
Throwing a tantrum the moment
your mischief comes to light?
You behave like an undisciplined child.
What's come over me?
The same girl still stands before me,
and yet I could almost...
Mark my words, Aisha Spencer.
Trying to fool me is far more
offensive than anything I said.
To whom do you imagine you're speaking?
Scarlett...?
No, I'd never mistake anyone for her.
Ten years ago, Scarlett Castiel
was the center of my world.
Her and her fiancé, Crown Prince Enrique.
They didn't share anything
as sweet as love,
but I noticed they were
comfortable together, like siblings.
How I idolized them.
But then she came along.
Talk of their star-crossed love in
defiance of status spread like wildfire.
I knew the rumors would become truth
unless someone stopped them.
I thought that I had to do
something. And just then...
What happened, Sharon?
You look so much thinner
than when I last saw you.
I used this.
It's supposed to be a kind of foreign
smelling salts. Worked wonders, didn't it?
One pinch is all it takes.
Taking too much is bad for your health.
I'd heard that Cecilia suffered from
a naturally frail constitution.
If she took ill, she'd have
to return to her family estate.
I put on my replica set of
Scarlett's moonbowstone earrings
and set out to pay a sympathy visit
to the Luze residence.
How was I to know Scarlett had come
and caused a scene mere hours earlier?
There it is!
I'll just pour the smelling salts
into this water.
I'm doing this for Scarlett.
I know she'd do the same.
If I were Scarlett, I'd...
If I do this, I can become Scarlett!
So you poisoned the water.
I had no idea it was poison.
It's true!
I still have the bottle I used back then!
Check it and you'll see
it's only a slimming drug!
It wasn't my fault!
So please! Forgive me, Scarlett!
You want my forgiveness?
Then why did you not confess your crime?
Whether it was poison or not
makes no difference.
Either way, you knew that I was innocent.
I went to the executioner
because of the crime you committed.
I... I did it for you!
You would have done the same thing
if you'd had the chance.
So in your place, I—
I...
I would rather die than do
anything so disgraceful.
Everything you did ten years ago,
you did for yourself.
Who do you think you are
to use me as your excuse?
Aisha Spencer,
just for you, I will ask one last time...
To whom do you imagine you're speaking?
Deep down, I knew.
The answer has been staring me
in the face all this time.
I merely shut my eyes to it
to spare myself.
I caused it all.
I...
killed Scarlett!
No!
What good will dying do?!
Your death won't undo
what you did to Scarlett!
You ought to live on and atone.
Lady Huxley?!
A few days later, Aisha Huxley
contacted the Mayflower Company,
saying she wanted to confess her crimes.
Translation:
William Varteresian
Are you all right?
Your Lordship?
Subtitle Timing:
Edgar Cruz
Subtitle Editing:
Riley Dalton
He came for me...
It was Aisha. She poisoned
the Luzes' water jar.
Quality Check:
SMR
Translation Check:
Sriram Gurunathan
Do you have anything to prove it?
She says she has the bottle of poison.
From ten years ago?
Verifying that will take time.
Also... she's been using
Jackal's Paradise.
So she does have dealings
with Daeg Gallus after all.
Yes.
Give me the details another time,
when you feel more yourself.
I'll escort you home.
I would appreciate that.
Why did you stop her?!
You should have just let her die!
Connie, you idiot! Why did you save her?!
She was the one! It was her fault that I—
And what if it was?!
The nerve of her,
looking to die over what you said!
How could I let her make you
her excuse right to the end?!
Besides...
we may lose our chance
at more clues if Aisha dies now.
Your revenge is nowhere
near complete, remember?
There's whoever switched the earrings,
and Lady Lily, and Daeg Gallus.
We haven't solved anything.
Listen, Scarlett. I...
I'll spend the rest of my life
ensuring that you have your revenge!
Sometimes, girl,
you have a way with words.
A line like that is too good for you.